[
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Where was Frida Kahlo born?", "answer": "Mexico"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Café Terrace at Night is an 1888 oil painting by which Dutch master?", "answer": "Vincent Van Gogh"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Where is the original Starry Night by Vincent Van Gogh housed?", "answer": "Museum of Modern Art, New York"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "In which century did Rembrandt live?", "answer": "17th"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "In what decade was celebrated artist Tracy Emin born?", "answer": "1960s"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Who painted The Scream in 1893?", "answer":  "Edvard Munch"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "The 1930 Grant Wood painting ‘American Gothic’ depicts a woman and a man holding what?", "answer":  "A pitchfork"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Name the artist that painted The Creation of Adam – the painting found on the Sistine Chapel’s ceiling.", "answer":  "Michelangelo"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Where is the Mona Lisa displayed?", "answer":  "The Louvre Museum, France"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Rene Magritte’s ‘The Son of Man’ depicts a man in a suit and bowler hat. Which fruit is covering his face?", "answer":  "Apple"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Who painted The Birth of Venus?", "answer":  "Sandro Botticelli"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What are the names of all four Tate galleries?", "answer":  "Tate Britain, Tate Modern, Tate Liverpool and Tate St Ives."},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "The Starry Night is a painting by which artist?", "answer":  "Vincent van Gogh"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Name the extravagant period of art and architecture prevalent in Europe during most of the 17th century?", "answer":  "The Baroque period"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which famous painter was also a sculptor, an architect, and an engineer?", "answer":  "Leonardo Da Vinci"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "The artist Kandinsky is considered the first for this type of art?", "answer":  "Abstract"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Claude Monet is most known for his paintings of what?", "answer":  "Water lily paintings"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which abstract expressionist was known for using the “drip technique?", "answer":  "Jackson Pollock"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which artist is most famous for their close-up perspective paintings of flowers?", "answer":  "Georgia O’Keeffe"},
    { "topic_id": 1, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which Spanish painter is referred to as both the last of the old masters and the moderns?", "answer":  "Francisco Goya"},


    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What is the name of The Bride, played by Uma Thurman, in Quentin Tarantino’s Kill Bill franchise?", "answer": "Beatrix Kiddo"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which colour pill does Neo swallow in The Matrix?", "answer": "Red"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which 2014 Seth Rogan film caused the North Korean government to threaten action against the United States?", "answer": "The Interview"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Name the first actor to play Dumbledore in the Harry Potter films. ", "answer": "Richard Harris"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which Catastrophe star makes a cameo in Deadpool 2 as Peter?", "answer": "Rob Delaney"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which husband-wife duo starred in 2018’s horror film A Quiet Place?", "answer": "Emily Blunt and John Krasinski"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which 2019 film won the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Film this year? ", "answer": "Cats"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What does Bridget Jones name her baby in the film series’s third instalment?", "answer": "William"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which three films make up what is known as the Three Flavours Cornetto Trilogy?", "answer": "Shaun of the Dead, Hot Fuzz, The World’s End"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Who starred as Neil Armstrong in Damien Chazelle's biopic First Man?", "answer": "Ryan Gosling"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which movie features an iconic dance scene between Uma Thurman and John Travolta?", "answer": "Pulp Fiction"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What is the name of the second James Bond film?", "answer": "From Russia With Love"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Inigo Montoya is a character from which 1987 Rob Reiner film?", "answer": "The Princess Bride"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Who directed Titanic, Avatar and The Terminator?", "answer": "James Cameron"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What year was the first Toy Story film released in cinemas?", "answer": "1995"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which actor broke two toes whilst filming The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers?", "answer": "Viggo Mortensen, whilst kicking a helmet."},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Who played the lead role in the 2001 film Lara Croft: Tomb Raider?", "answer": "Angelina Jolie"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "The Magnificent Seven is a remake of which iconic Japanese film?", "answer": "Seven Samurai"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Russell Crowe turned down the role of which character in Peter Jackson’s Lord of the Rings trilogy?", "answer": "Aragorn"},
    { "topic_id": 2, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Who directed the movie ‘The Shining’?", "answer": "Stanley Kubrick"},

    { "topic_id": 3, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which soft drink is commonly associated with Scotland?", "answer": "Irn-Bru"},
    { "topic_id": 3, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What are the two main ingredients of a Dark and Stormy cocktail?", "answer": "Dark rum, Ginger Beer"},
    { "topic_id": 3, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Gouda is a popular cheese originating from which country?", "answer": "The Netherlands"},
    { "topic_id": 3, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "A screwdriver cocktail is orange juice, ice and which spirit?", "answer": "Vodka"},
    { "topic_id": 3, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which southern Italian city is usually credited as the birthplace of the pizza?", "answer": "Naples"},
    { "topic_id": 3, "difficulty_id": 1, "question": "What number is found in reference to their varieties on Heinz products?", "answer": "57"},
    { "topic_id": 3, "difficulty_id": 1, "question": "What is James Bond's favourite tipple?", "answer": "Vodka Martini – shaken not stirred"},
    { "topic_id": 3, "difficulty_id": 1, "question": "What is the most consumed manufactured drink in the world?", "answer": "Tea"},
    { "topic_id": 3, "difficulty_id": 1, "question": "Which foul-mouthed chef hosted the Kitchen Nightmares series?", "answer": "Gordon Ramsay"},
    { "topic_id": 3, "difficulty_id": 1, "question": "What type of wheat is used to make pasta?", "answer": "Durum"},
    { "topic_id": 3, "difficulty_id": 1, "question": "What French city does bouillabaisse originate from?", "answer": "Marseille"},
    { "topic_id": 3, "difficulty_id": 1, "question": "What spirit is mixed with ginger beer in a Moscow mule?", "answer": "Vodka"},
    

    { "topic_id": 4, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "In which part of your body would you find the cruciate ligament?", "answer": "Knee"},
    { "topic_id": 4, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What was the most popular girls name in the UK in 2019?", "answer": "Olivia"},
    { "topic_id": 4, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Continental United States has 4 time zones, can you name them?", "answer": "Pacific, Mountain, Central, Eastern"},
    { "topic_id": 4, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What is the currency of Denmark?", "answer": "Krone"},
    { "topic_id": 4, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which popular video game franchise has released games with the subtitles World At War and Black Ops?", "answer": "Call of Duty"},

    { "topic_id": 5, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What is the capital city of Australia?", "answer": "Canberra"},
    { "topic_id": 5, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "If you completed the Three Peaks challenge, which three UK mountains would you have climbed?", "answer": "Ben Nevis, Snowdon, Scafell Pike"},
    { "topic_id": 5, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which UK city is situated further west – Bristol or Edinburgh?", "answer": "Edinburgh"},
    { "topic_id": 5, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What is the capital of Finland?", "answer": "Helsinki"},
    { "topic_id": 5, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What is the capital of Malta?", "answer": "Valetta"},

    { "topic_id": 6, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Queen Elizabeth II is the longest reigning monarch of the UK, followed by Queen Victoria – but who is third?", "answer": "George III"},
    { "topic_id": 6, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which two houses were involved in the War of the Roses?", "answer": "York, Lancaster"},
    { "topic_id": 6, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Who was the second President of the United States?", "answer": "John Adams"},
    { "topic_id": 6, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which war was fought in South Africa between 1899 and 1902?", "answer": "Second Boer War (Allow Boer War)"},
    { "topic_id": 6, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which ship is notorious for experiencing the bloodiest mutiny in British naval history?", "answer": "HMS Hermione"},

    { "topic_id": 7, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which Stephen King novel takes place mostly in the fictional Overlook Hotel?", "answer": "The Shining"},
    { "topic_id": 7, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What is the best-selling novel of all time?", "answer": "Don Quixote"},
    { "topic_id": 7, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "In Pride and Prejudice, who does Jane Bennet marry?", "answer": "Charles Bingley"},
    { "topic_id": 7, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What do Lord of the Rings author J.R.R. Tolkien’s initials stand for?", "answer": "John Ronald Reuel"},
    { "topic_id": 7, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Name all five Brontë sisters.", "answer": "Emily, Elizabeth, Charlotte, Anne and Maria"},

    { "topic_id": 8, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Matt Goss, Luke Goss and Craig Logan made up which band?", "answer": "Bros"},
    { "topic_id": 8, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "In what year did Elvis Presley die?", "answer": "1977 "},
    { "topic_id": 8, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Gary and Martin Kemp were in what band?", "answer": "Spandau Ballet"},
    { "topic_id": 8, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which comedy double act scored a huge hit with the England football anthem Three Lions in 1996?", "answer": "David Baddiel and Frank Skinner"},
    { "topic_id": 8, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "In what year did The Beatles split up?", "answer": "1970"},

    { "topic_id": 9, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "In 1952 Albert Einstein was offered the Presidency of which country?", "answer": "Israel"},
    { "topic_id": 9, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What year did Britain join the EEC, now knows as the European Union?", "answer": "1973"},
    { "topic_id": 9, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What colour are the seats in the House of Commons?", "answer": "Green"},
    { "topic_id": 9, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which former British Prime Minister graduated from Oxford University in 1947 with Second-Class Honours in Chemistry?", "answer": "Margaret Thatcher"},
    { "topic_id": 9, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What is the official name of the clock tower commonly referred to as Big Ben?", "answer": "Elizabeth Tower"},

    { "topic_id": 10, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What does DNA stand for?", "answer": "Deoxyribonucleic acid"},
    { "topic_id": 10, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which is the main gas that makes up the Earth’s atmosphere?", "answer": "Nitrogen"},
    { "topic_id": 10, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which famous British physicist wrote A Brief History of Time?\n", "answer": "Stephen Hawking"},
    { "topic_id": 10, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What name is given for the number of protons found in the nucleus of an atom?", "answer": "Atomic number"},
    { "topic_id": 10, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What was the name of the first man-made satellite launched by the Soviet Union in 1957?", "answer": "Sputnik 1"},

    { "topic_id": 11, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Jurgen Klopp began his managerial career at which German club?", "answer": "Mainz 05"},
    { "topic_id": 11, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "In which year did Roger Federer win his first Wimbledon title?", "answer": "2003"},
    { "topic_id": 11, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What is Muhammad Ali’s real name?", "answer": "Cassius Clay"},
    { "topic_id": 11, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "In rugby union, who is England Men’s all-time top try scorer?", "answer": "Rory Underwood"},
    { "topic_id": 11, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "The Los Angeles Lakers and New York Knicks play which sport?", "answer": "Basketball"},

    { "topic_id": 12, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What does the term LASER stand for?", "answer": "Light Amplification by Stimulated Emission of Radiation"},
    { "topic_id": 12, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What does CPU stand for?", "answer": "Central Processing Unit"},
    { "topic_id": 12, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What unit of length is equal to around 5.8 trillion miles?", "answer": "Light Year"},
    { "topic_id": 12, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "What is the name of the British computer scientist who invented the World Wide Web in 1989?", "answer": "Tim Berners-Lee"},
    { "topic_id": 12, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which duo invented the aeroplane?", "answer": "The Wright Brothers – Orville and Wilbur Wright"},

    { "topic_id": 13, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "The Spanish Steps are in which city?", "answer": "Rome"},
    { "topic_id": 13, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "O’Hare Airport serves which American city?", "answer": "Chicago"},
    { "topic_id": 13, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Grand Canyon National Park is in which US state?", "answer": "Arizona"},
    { "topic_id": 13, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "On the London Underground map, which line is the colour black?", "answer": "Northern Line"},
    { "topic_id": 13, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Where can you visit Tivoli Gardens?", "answer": "Copenhagen"},

    { "topic_id": 14, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "US sitcom Frasier (1993-2004) is a spin-off series from which popular comedy?", "answer": "Cheers"},
    { "topic_id": 14, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "How many episodes of Game of Thrones are there?", "answer": "73"},
    { "topic_id": 14, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Which British TV show recorded the largest audience for a single episode with over 30 million viewers?", "answer": "Eastenders (on Christmas Day 1986)"},
    { "topic_id": 14, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "Who played Rodney Trotter in Only Fools and Horses?", "answer": "Nicholas Lyndhurst"},
    { "topic_id": 14, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "In which fictional town is Netflix show Stranger Things primarily set?", "answer": "Hawkins, Indiana"},
    { "topic_id": 14, "difficulty_id": 3, "question": "In what year did Coronation Street first air on ITV?", "answer": "1960" }


]
